(Penny:)Sheldon, what did you say?
The truth. You don't wanna live
with Leonard and you know it.
- Since when don't you want to live with me?
- You decided to move in...
(Penny:)...without even asking me if I was ready.
- I think we should talk about that.
(Penny:)Since you love the truth so much...
...why not tell Amy you don't wanna
live with her instead of blaming me?
(Sheldon:)I thought we were talking about
the other thing.
- You're a coward.
- Well, the evidence does support that.
(Penny:)Come on, Amy. Let's go drink wine and talk
about what jerks our boyfriends are.
(Amy:)You know what would show them?
I should move in here with you.
(Leonard:)Um...
So you wanna catch up
on some Walking Dead?
(Sheldon:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)Have you seen the one where Lori dies?
(Leonard:)No.
(Sheldon:)Or maybe she doesn't, let's find out.
- Where are you going?
- No!